Guide to the Josephine Harris Stewart Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Ephemera
  - Conference Items
    - AIDS '89: The Social Work Response conference pouch, 1989 (Box 20, Item 3)
    - Ms. Magazine tote bag, undated (Box 20, Item 4)
    - A Woman's Place is in the House…and in the Senate tote bag, undated (Box 20, Item 5)
    - NOW National Conference Delegate Identification Badge, 1980 (Box 20, Item 6)
  - Newspapers
    - Cincinnati Enquirer (3), July 16, 1979 (Box 21, Item 1)
    - The Sentinal, June 13, 1980 (Box 21, Item 2)
  - Plaques
    - Distinguished Service Award - NASW National Committee on Gay and Lesbian Issues, 1985 (Box 21, Item 1)
    - NASW Social Worker of the Year Award, 1986 (Box 21, Item 2)
    - Social Work Certification, 1989 (Box 21, Item 3)
    - NASW Academy Member, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Item 4)
    - NASW Pioneer Award, undated (Box 21, Item 5)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Methodist Hospital identification badge, undated (Box 21, Item 1)
    - Name/Deskplate, undated (Box 21, Item 2)
    - Social Workers for Peace and Nuclear Disarmament bumper sticker, undated (Box 21, Item 3)
    - The Pines Country Club Women's Golf Association three-ring binder, undated (Box 21, Item 4)
  - Posters
    - Presidential Appointees - autographed by Sarah Weddington, 1979 (Drawer F.8, Ovs folder 5)
    - Social Work: A Family Matter - NASW, Texas Chapter, undated (Drawer F.8, Ovs folder 5)
    - Feminism Spoken Here, undated (Drawer F.8, Ovs folder 5)
    - Gloria Steinem speaking on Racism and Sexism - University of Houston Clear Lake, undated (Drawer F.8, Ovs folder 5)
    - Women's Week V - University of Houston Clear Lake, undated (Drawer F.8, Ovs folder 5)